export const heyear9qs = [
  {
    question: "What is the function of Calcium",
    answer: "ONEOF(BONE_TEETH)",
    help: "Growth and maintenance strong bones and teeth",
  },
  {
    question: "Name a source of Calcium",
    answer: "ONEOF(CHEESE_MILK_YOGURT_GREEN_DAIRY)",
    help: "Cheese, milk, yogurt, green leafy vegetables",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function of Vitamin C",
    answer: "ONEOF(SKIN_TISSUE)",
    help: "Maintenance healthy skin, maintains body connective tissue",
  },
  {
    question: "Name a source of Vitamin C",
    answer: "CONTAINS(CITRUS)",
    help: "Citrus fruit",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function of B group vitamins",
    answer: "CONTAINS(RELEAS)ANDCONTAINS(ENERGY)",
    help: "Helps Release Energy",
  },
  {
    question: "Name a source of B group vitamins",
    answer: "ONEOF(RED MEAT_DAIRY_GREEN_FORTIFIED BREAKFAST CEREAL)",
    help: "Red meat, dairy, green leafy vegetables",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function of Vitamin A",
    answer: "ONEOF(NIGHT VISION_SKIN_TISSUE)",
    help: "Night Vision, healthy skin and tissue",
  },
  {
    question: "Name a source of Vitamin A",
    answer: "ONEOF(CARROT_MILK_EGGS_LIVER)",
    help: "Carrots, milk, eggs, liver",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function of Vitamin D",
    answer: "ONEOF(CALCIUM_BONES_TEETH)",
    help: "Helps absorb calcium, strong bones and teeth",
  },
  {
    question: "Name a source of Vitamin D",
    answer: "ONEOF(SUN_MARGARINE_EGGS_FORTIFIED BREAKFAST CEREAL)",
    help: "Sunlight, margarine, eggs, fortified breakfast cereals",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a consumer?",
    answer: "ONEOF(PURCHASE_BUY)",
    help: "A person who purchases goods or services for personal use",
  },
  {
    question: "How to avoid food waste?",
    answer: "ONEOF(PLAN_BUY_DATE_FREEZE_FROZEN_BEST_LEFTOVERS_FRIDGE_OLD)",
    help: "Good planning oldest dates use first, plan meals, don't buy too much, buy good dates, don't cook too much, use food best before, use leftovers, keep in the fridge, if it's not going to be used can it be frozen",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Consumer Rights Act 2015: When buying goods the law gives you rights as a ________?",
    answer: "CONTAINS(CONSUMER)",
    help: "Consumer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Consumer Rights Act: The law states that goods must be satisfactory _______?",
    answer: "CONTAINS(QUALITY)",
    help: "Satisfactory Quality: not faulty or damaged",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Consumer Rights Act: The law states that goods must be fit for _______?",
    answer: "CONTAINS(PURPOSE)",
    help: "Fit for Purpose: do what they say",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Consumer Rights Act: The law states that goods must be as _________?",
    answer: "CONTAINS(DESCRIBED)",
    help: "As Described: match description",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Consumer Rights Act 2015, If the goods are not satisfactory quality, fit for purpose or as described, what can you do?",
    answer: "ONEOF(RETURN_SHOP_RECEIPT_MANAGER_PROBLEM_CAB_CITIZEN_BUREAU)",
    help: "Return to shop, show receipt to manager, explain problem, if it didn't solve you can contact CAB Citizens Advice Bureau",
  },
];
